export const EventLocale = {
    "default": {
        "locale": "en-us",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "email": "Email Address",
        "name": "Name",
        "phone": "Phone",
        "phone-helper": "Your phone should be in the format '+12345678' with the country code.",
        "artists": "Artists",
        "country": "Country",
        "city": "City",
        "when": "When",
        "related": "Other episodes from our guests",
        "episodes": "Listen to this event's episodes",
        "back": "Back to events",
        "countdown": "Countdown",
        "photos": "Photos",
        "local": "Local time",
        "already": "You're already registered for this event, hope to see you there!",
        "register": "Click here to add your name to the list",
        "buy": "Click here to buy tickets",
        "calendar": "Add to calendar",
        "or": "Or, add your name to the event discount list:",
        "reset": "Reset filters",
        "countries": "Countries",
        "events": "Events",
        "eventsDescription": "A list of our events. Brought with love to your boroughs.",
        "D": "Day",
        "W": "Week",
        "Q": "Quarter",
        "M": "Month",
        "timeframe": "Timeframe",
        "space": "Space",
        "time": "Time",
        "know": "Know more at",
        "brought": "Brought to you by",
        "T": "Today",
        "L": "List",
        "allDay": "all day",
        "terms": "Terms",
        "calendarPrompt": "Would you like to add this event to your calendar?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Would you like to be redirected to the event page?",
        "ctaMessage": "Don't see your event?",
        "sendEmail": "Add it",
        "mode": "Switch view"
    },
    "it-it": {
        "locale": "it-it",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "email": "Indirizzo e-mail",
        "name": "Nome",
        "phone": "Numero di cellulare",
        "phone-helper": "Il tuo telefono deve essere nel formato '+393123123123', con il prefisso del paese.",
        "artists": "Artisti",
        "country": "Nazione",
        "city": "Città",
        "when": "Quando",
        "related": "Altri episodi dei nostri ospiti",
        "episodes": "Ascolta gli episodi di questo evento",
        "back": "Vedi altri eventi",
        "countdown": "Conto alla rovescia",
        "photos": "Fotografie",
        "local": "Ora locale",
        "already": "Sei già registrato per questo evento, spero di vederti lì!",
        "register": "Clicca qui per iscriverti alla lista dell'evento.",
        "buy": "Clicca qui per acquistare i biglietti",
        "calendar": "Aggiungi a calendario",
        "or": "Oppure, iscriverti alla lista sconti dell'evento:",
        "reset": "Ripristina filtri",
        "countries": "Paesi",
        "events": "Eventi",
        "eventsDescription": "Un elenco dei nostri eventi. Portato con amore nei tuoi quartieri.",
        "D": "Giorno",
        "W": "Settimana",
        "Q": "Trimestre",
        "M": "Mese",
        "timeframe": "Arco temporale",
        "space": "Spazio",
        "time": "Tempo",
        "know": "Scopri di più su",
        "brought": "Portato a voi da",
        "T": "Oggi",
        "L": "Lista",
        "allDay": "tutto il giorno",
        "terms": "Termini",
        "calendarPrompt": "Vuoi aggiungere questo evento al tuo calendario?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Vuoi essere reindirizzato alla pagina dell'evento?",
        "ctaMessage": "Non vedi il tuo evento?",
        "sendEmail": "Aggiungilo",
        "mode": "Cambia visualizzazione"
    },
    "pt-br": {
        "locale": "pt-br",
        "timezone": "America/Bahia",
        "email": "Endereço de email",
        "name": "Nome",
        "phone": "Celular",
        "phone-helper": "Seu telefone deve estar no formato '+5571991234567', com o código do país e da cidade.",
        "artists": "Artistas",
        "country": "País",
        "city": "Cidade",
        "when": "Quando",
        "related": "Outros episódios por nossos convidados",
        "episodes": "Escute os episódios desse evento",
        "back": "Veja outros eventos",
        "countdown": "Contagem regressiva",
        "photos": "Fotos",
        "local": "Horário local",
        "already": "Você já se inscreveu para este evento, espero ver-te lá!",
        "register": "Clique aqui e adicione seu nome na lista",
        "buy": "Clique aqui para comprar ingressos",
        "calendar": "Adicione ao calendário",
        "or": "Ou adicione seu nome na lista de desconto:",
        "reset": "Redefinir filtros",
        "countries": "Países",
        "events": "Eventos",
        "eventsDescription": "Uma lista de nossos eventos. Trazidos com amor para seus bairros.",
        "D": "Dia",
        "W": "Semana",
        "Q": "Trimestre",
        "M": "Mês",
        "timeframe": "Período",
        "space": "Espaço",
        "time": "Tempo",
        "know": "Saiba mais em",
        "brought": "Trazido até você por",
        "T": "Hoje",
        "L": "Lista",
        "allDay": "o dia todo",
        "terms": "Termos",
        "calendarPrompt": "Você quer adicionar este evento ao seu calendário?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Você quer ser redirecionado para a página do evento?",
        "ctaMessage": "Não vê seu evento?",
        "sendEmail": "Adicione-o",
        "mode": "Mudar visualização"
    },
    "es-es": {
        "locale": "es-es",
        "timezone": "Europe/Madrid",
        "email": "Dirección de correo",
        "name": "Nombre",
        "phone": "Teléfono",
        "phone-helper": "Tu teléfono debe estar en el formato '+34911234567', con el código del país.",
        "artists": "Artistas",
        "country": "País",
        "city": "Ciudad",
        "when": "Cuándo",
        "related": "Otros episodios de nuestros invitados",
        "episodes": "Escucha los episodios de este evento",
        "back": "Ver otros eventos",
        "countdown": "Cuenta regresiva",
        "photos": "Fotos",
        "local": "Hora local",
        "already": "Ya estás inscrito para este evento, ¡esperamos verte allí!",
        "register": "Haz clic aquí para añadir tu nombre a la lista",
        "buy": "Haz clic aquí para comprar entradas",
        "calendar": "Añadir al calendario",
        "or": "O añade tu nombre a la lista de descuentos del evento:",
        "reset": "Restablecer filtros",
        "countries": "Países",
        "events": "Eventos",
        "eventsDescription": "Una lista de nuestros eventos. Traído con amor a tus barrios.",
        "D": "Día",
        "W": "Semana",
        "Q": "Trimestre",
        "M": "Mes",
        "timeframe": "Periodo de tiempo",
        "space": "Espacio",
        "time": "Tiempo",
        "know": "Conoce más en",
        "brought": "Traído a ti por",
        "T": "Hoy",
        "L": "Lista",
        "allDay": "todo el día",
        "terms": "Términos",
        "calendarPrompt": "¿Quieres agregar este evento a tu calendario?",
        "redirectPrompt": "¿Quieres ser redirigido a la página del evento?",
        "ctaMessage": "¿No ves tu evento?",
        "sendEmail": "Añádelo",
        "mode": "Cambiar vista"
    },
    "de-de": {
        "locale": "de-de",
        "timezone": "Europe/Berlin",
        "email": "E-Mail-Adresse",
        "name": "Name",
        "phone": "Telefon",
        "phone-helper": "Ihre Telefonnummer sollte im Format '+49123456789' mit der Ländervorwahl sein.",
        "artists": "Künstler",
        "country": "Land",
        "city": "Stadt",
        "when": "Wann",
        "related": "Weitere Episoden von unseren Gästen",
        "episodes": "Hören Sie die Episoden dieses Events",
        "back": "Zurück zu den Veranstaltungen",
        "countdown": "Countdown",
        "photos": "Fotos",
        "local": "Ortszeit",
        "already": "Du bist bereits für diese Veranstaltung angemeldet, wir hoffen, dich dort zu sehen!",
        "register": "Klicken Sie hier, um Ihren Namen zur Liste hinzuzufügen",
        "buy": "Klicken Sie hier, um Tickets zu kaufen",
        "calendar": "Zum Kalender hinzufügen",
        "or": "Oder fügen Sie Ihren Namen zur Rabattliste des Events hinzu:",
        "reset": "Filter zurücksetzen",
        "countries": "Länder",
        "events": "Veranstaltungen",
        "eventsDescription": "Eine Liste unserer Veranstaltungen. Mit Liebe in deine Bezirke gebracht.",
        "D": "Tag",
        "W": "Woche",
        "Q": "Quartal",
        "M": "Monat",
        "timeframe": "Zeitraum",
        "space": "Raum",
        "time": "Zeit",
        "know": "Erfahren Sie mehr unter",
        "brought": "Präsentiert von",
        "T": "Heute",
        "L": "Liste",
        "allDay": "ganztägig",
        "terms": "Bedingungen",
        "calendarPrompt": "Möchten Sie diese Veranstaltung zu Ihrem Kalender hinzufügen?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Möchten Sie zur Veranstaltungsseite weitergeleitet werden?",
        "ctaMessage": "Siehst du dein Event nicht?",
        "sendEmail": "Füge es hinzu",
        "mode": "Ansicht wechseln"
    },
    "fr-fr": {
        "locale": "fr-fr",
        "timezone": "Europe/Paris",
        "email": "Adresse e-mail",
        "name": "Nom",
        "phone": "Téléphone",
        "phone-helper": "Votre téléphone doit être au format '+33123456789', avec l'indicatif du pays.",
        "artists": "Artistes",
        "country": "Pays",
        "city": "Ville",
        "when": "Quand",
        "related": "Autres épisodes de nos invités",
        "episodes": "Écoutez les épisodes de cet événement",
        "back": "Voir d'autres événements",
        "countdown": "Compte à rebours",
        "photos": "Photos",
        "local": "Heure locale",
        "already": "Vous êtes déjà inscrit à cet événement, espérons vous y voir !",
        "register": "Cliquez ici pour ajouter votre nom à la liste",
        "buy": "Cliquez ici pour acheter des billets",
        "calendar": "Ajouter au calendrier",
        "or": "Ou ajoutez votre nom à la liste de réduction de l'événement:",
        "reset": "Réinitialiser les filtres",
        "countries": "Pays",
        "events": "Événements",
        "eventsDescription": "Une liste de nos événements. Apportée avec amour dans vos quartiers.",
        "D": "Jour",
        "W": "Semaine",
        "Q": "Trimestre",
        "M": "Mois",
        "timeframe": "Période",
        "space": "Espace",
        "time": "Temps",
        "know": "En savoir plus sur",
        "brought": "Présenté par",
        "T": "Aujourd'hui",
        "L": "Liste",
        "allDay": "toute la journée",
        "terms": "Termes",
        "calendarPrompt": "Voulez-vous ajouter cet événement à votre calendrier?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Voulez-vous être redirigé vers la page de l'événement?",
        "ctaMessage": "Vous ne voyez pas votre événement?",
        "sendEmail": "Ajoutez-le",
        "mode": "Changer de vue"
    },
    "ro": {
        "locale": "ro",
        "timezone": "Europe/Bucharest",
        "email": "Adresa de email",
        "name": "Nume",
        "phone": "Telefon",
        "phone-helper": "Numărul tău de telefon ar trebui să fie în formatul '+40123456789', cu codul țării.",
        "artists": "Artiști",
        "country": "Țară",
        "city": "Oraș",
        "when": "Când",
        "related": "Alte episoade cu invitații noștri",
        "episodes": "Ascultă episoadele acestui eveniment",
        "back": "Înapoi la evenimente",
        "countdown": "Numărătoare inversă",
        "photos": "Fotografii",
        "local": "Ora locală",
        "already": "Ești deja înregistrat pentru acest eveniment, sper să te văd acolo!",
        "register": "Apasă aici pentru a-ți adăuga numele în listă",
        "buy": "Apasă aici pentru a cumpăra bilete",
        "calendar": "Adaugă în calendar",
        "or": "Sau, adaugă-ți numele în lista de reduceri a evenimentului:",
        "reset": "Resetează filtrele",
        "countries": "Țări",
        "events": "Evenimente",
        "eventsDescription": "O listă a evenimentelor noastre. Adusă cu dragoste în cartierele tale.",
        "D": "Zi",
        "W": "Săptămână",
        "Q": "Trimestru",
        "M": "Lună",
        "timeframe": "Perioadă de timp",
        "space": "Spațiu",
        "time": "Timp",
        "know": "Aflați mai multe la",
        "brought": "Adus pentru tine de",
        "T": "Astăzi",
        "L": "Listă",
        "allDay": "toată ziua",
        "terms": "Termeni",
        "calendarPrompt": "Doriți să adăugați acest eveniment în calendarul dvs?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Doriți să fiți redirecționat către pagina evenimentului?",
        "ctaMessage": "Nu vezi evenimentul tău?",
        "sendEmail": "Adaugă-l",
        "mode": "Schimbă vizualizarea"
    },
    "pl-pl": {
        "locale": "pl-pl",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "email": "Adres e-mail",
        "name": "Imię",
        "phone": "Telefon",
        "phone-helper": "Twój numer telefonu powinien mieć format '+12345678' z kodem kraju.",
        "artists": "Artyści",
        "country": "Kraj",
        "city": "Miasto",
        "when": "Kiedy",
        "related": "Inne odcinki z naszymi gośćmi",
        "episodes": "Słuchaj odcinków z tego wydarzenia",
        "back": "Powrót do wydarzeń",
        "countdown": "Odliczanie",
        "photos": "Zdjęcia",
        "local": "Czas lokalny",
        "already": "Jesteś już zarejestrowany na to wydarzenie, mamy nadzieję, że się tam zobaczymy!",
        "register": "Kliknij tutaj, aby dodać swoje imię do listy",
        "buy": "Kliknij tutaj, aby kupić bilety",
        "calendar": "Dodaj do kalendarza",
        "or": "Lub dodaj swoje imię do listy zniżek na wydarzenie:",
        "reset": "Zresetuj filtry",
        "countries": "Kraje",
        "events": "Wydarzenia",
        "eventsDescription": "Lista naszych wydarzeń. Przygotowane z miłością do twoich dzielnic.",
        "D": "Dzień",
        "W": "Tydzień",
        "Q": "Kwartał",
        "M": "Miesiąc",
        "timeframe": "Okres czasu",
        "space": "Przestrzeń",
        "time": "Czas",
        "know": "Dowiedz się więcej na",
        "brought": "Przedstawione przez",
        "T": "Dziś",
        "L": "Lista",
        "allDay": "Cały dzień",
        "terms": "Warunki",
        "calendarPrompt": "Czy chcesz dodać to wydarzenie do swojego kalendarza?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Czy chcesz zostać przekierowany na stronę wydarzenia?",
        "ctaMessage": "Nie widzisz swojego wydarzenia?",
        "sendEmail": "Dodaj je",
        "mode": "Zmień widok"
    },
    "cs-cz": {
        "locale": "cs-cz",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "email": "E-mailová adresa",
        "name": "Jméno",
        "phone": "Telefon",
        "phone-helper": "Váš telefon by měl mít formát '+12345678' s kódem země.",
        "artists": "Umělci",
        "country": "Země",
        "city": "Město",
        "when": "Kdy",
        "related": "Další epizody od našich hostů",
        "episodes": "Poslouchejte epizody z této události",
        "back": "Zpět na události",
        "countdown": "Odpočítávání",
        "photos": "Fotografie",
        "local": "Místní čas",
        "already": "Na tuto událost jste již registrováni, těšíme se na vás!",
        "register": "Klikněte zde, abyste se přidali na seznam",
        "buy": "Klikněte zde pro nákup vstupenek",
        "calendar": "Přidat do kalendáře",
        "or": "Nebo se přidejte na seznam slev k události:",
        "reset": "Resetovat filtry",
        "countries": "Země",
        "events": "Události",
        "eventsDescription": "Seznam našich událostí. S láskou pro vaše obvody.",
        "D": "Den",
        "W": "Týden",
        "Q": "Čtvrtletí",
        "M": "Měsíc",
        "timeframe": "Časový rámec",
        "space": "Prostor",
        "time": "Čas",
        "know": "Více informací na",
        "brought": "Přináší vám",
        "T": "Dnes",
        "L": "Seznam",
        "allDay": "Celý den",
        "terms": "Podmínky",
        "calendarPrompt": "Chcete přidat tuto událost do svého kalendáře?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Chcete být přesměrováni na stránku události?",
        "ctaMessage": "Nevidíte svou událost?",
        "sendEmail": "Přidejte ji",
        "mode": "Změnit zobrazení"
    },
    "sv-se": {
        "locale": "sv-se",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "email": "E-postadress",
        "name": "Namn",
        "phone": "Telefon",
        "phone-helper": "Ditt telefonnummer ska vara i formatet '+12345678' med landskod.",
        "artists": "Artister",
        "country": "Land",
        "city": "Stad",
        "when": "När",
        "related": "Andra avsnitt från våra gäster",
        "episodes": "Lyssna på detta evenemangs avsnitt",
        "back": "Tillbaka till evenemang",
        "countdown": "Nedräkning",
        "photos": "Foton",
        "local": "Lokal tid",
        "already": "Du är redan registrerad för detta evenemang, hoppas vi ses där!",
        "register": "Klicka här för att lägga till ditt namn i listan",
        "buy": "Klicka här för att köpa biljetter",
        "calendar": "Lägg till i kalender",
        "or": "Eller, lägg till ditt namn i evenemangets rabattlista:",
        "reset": "Återställ filter",
        "countries": "Länder",
        "events": "Evenemang",
        "eventsDescription": "En lista över våra evenemang. Levererat med kärlek till dina stadsdelar.",
        "D": "Dag",
        "W": "Vecka",
        "Q": "Kvartal",
        "M": "Månad",
        "timeframe": "Tidsram",
        "space": "Utrymme",
        "time": "Tid",
        "know": "Läs mer på",
        "brought": "Presenteras av",
        "T": "Idag",
        "L": "Lista",
        "allDay": "Hela dagen",
        "terms": "Villkor",
        "calendarPrompt": "Vill du lägga till denna händelse i din kalender?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Vill du omdirigeras till evenemangssidan?",
        "ctaMessage": "Ser du inte ditt evenemang?",
        "sendEmail": "Lägg till det",
        "mode": "Byt vy"
    },
    "et-ee": {
        "locale": "et-ee",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "email": "E-posti aadress",
        "name": "Nimi",
        "phone": "Telefon",
        "phone-helper": "Teie telefoninumber peaks olema formaadis '+12345678' koos riigikoodiga.",
        "artists": "Kunstnikud",
        "country": "Riik",
        "city": "Linn",
        "when": "Millal",
        "related": "Teised episoodid meie külalistelt",
        "episodes": "Kuula selle sündmuse episoode",
        "back": "Tagasi ürituste juurde",
        "countdown": "Loendur",
        "photos": "Fotod",
        "local": "Kohalik aeg",
        "already": "Olete juba sellele üritusele registreerunud, loodame teid seal näha!",
        "register": "Klõpsake siin, et lisada oma nimi nimekirja",
        "buy": "Klõpsake siin, et osta pileteid",
        "calendar": "Lisa kalendrisse",
        "or": "Või lisage oma nimi ürituse soodustuste nimekirja:",
        "reset": "Lähtesta filtrid",
        "countries": "Riigid",
        "events": "Üritused",
        "eventsDescription": "Nimekiri meie üritustest. Toome armastusega teie linnaosadesse.",
        "D": "Päev",
        "W": "Nädal",
        "Q": "Kvartal",
        "M": "Kuu",
        "timeframe": "Ajaraam",
        "space": "Ruum",
        "time": "Aeg",
        "know": "Rohkem teavet leiate",
        "brought": "Teieni toob",
        "T": "Täna",
        "L": "Nimekiri",
        "allDay": "Terve päev",
        "terms": "Tingimused",
        "calendarPrompt": "Kas soovite selle sündmuse oma kalendrisse lisada?",
        "redirectPrompt": "Kas soovite suunata sündmuse lehele?",
        "ctaMessage": "Ei näe oma sündmust?",
        "sendEmail": "Lisa see",
        "mode": "Vaheta vaadet"
    },
    "ja-jp": {
        "locale": "ja-jp",
        "timezone": "Europe/Rome",
        "email": "メールアドレス",
        "name": "名前",
        "phone": "電話",
        "phone-helper": "電話番号は国コードを含む '+12345678' の形式である必要があります。",
        "artists": "アーティスト",
        "country": "国",
        "city": "市",
        "when": "いつ",
        "related": "ゲストからの他のエピソード",
        "episodes": "このイベントのエピソードを聴く",
        "back": "イベントに戻る",
        "countdown": "カウントダウン",
        "photos": "写真",
        "local": "現地時間",
        "already": "すでにこのイベントに登録されています、お待ちしています！",
        "register": "リストに名前を追加するにはこちらをクリック",
        "buy": "チケットを購入するにはこちらをクリック",
        "calendar": "カレンダーに追加",
        "or": "または、イベントの割引リストに名前を追加してください：",
        "reset": "フィルターをリセット",
        "countries": "国々",
        "events": "イベント",
        "eventsDescription": "私たちのイベントのリスト。あなたの地区への愛を込めて。",
        "D": "日",
        "W": "週",
        "Q": "四半期",
        "M": "月",
        "timeframe": "期間",
        "space": "スペース",
        "time": "時間",
        "know": "詳しくはこちらで",
        "brought": "提供元：",
        "T": "今日",
        "L": "リスト",
        "allDay": "終日",
        "terms": "利用規約",
        "calendarPrompt": "このイベントをカレンダーに追加しますか？",
        "redirectPrompt": "イベントページにリダイレクトしますか？",
        "ctaMessage": "イベントが見えませんか？",
        "sendEmail": "追加してください",
        "mode": "表示切替"
    },
    "country": {
        "Brazil": "pt-br",
        "Italy": "it-it",
        "Spain": "es-es",
        "Germany": "de-de",
        "France": "fr-fr",
        "Romania": "ro",
        "Poland": "pl-pl",
        "Czech Republic": "cs-cz",
        "Sweden": "sv-se",
        "Estonia": "et-ee",
        "Japan": "ja-jp",
        "default": "en-us"
    }
}
